Evaluation Only. Created with Aspose. Words. Copyright 2003-2020 Aspose Pty Ltd.

Andrii Borozdykh

Java Developer

Email: <u>aborozdykh@gmail.com</u>

Mobile: +380 (67) 220-81-97 (Telegram)

Skype: andrey.borozdykh Location: Kyiv, Ukraine

GitHub: https://github.com/aborozdykh

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrii-borozdykh/

Summary

Highly motivated Software Engineer, with a background in support engineering and system administration, who obtained good knowledge and experience in Java programming, including such additional skills as resolving product or service problems, determining the cause of the problem, diagnosis of non-obvious problems and finding solutions for solving them. In total I have 10+ years in IT, have strong knowledge of OOP, Java Core, Java 8, and have worked mainly with JDBC, Hibernate, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Spring, Maven, Git, Docker, Kubernetes, Oracle ATG, etc. Also, I am well familiar with the Linux server administration and learning AWS development now.

I am comfortable to talk to, as well as I can easily find common ground with anybody. Becoming a part of any team, I would like to bring benefits in solving business problems. I can prove myself as an accurate, hard-working and reliable team member

Technical skills

- OOP, Design patterns
- SOLID, KISS and DRY principles
- Java Core, Java 8, Servlets, JSP, JSTL, Tomcat, JDBC, Log4j
- Hibernate, JPA, JUnit, Spring MVC/Security/Boot
- SQL basic knowledge (MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL)
- Web basic knowledge (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap)
- Git, Maven
- Linux: ssh, iptables, LAMP, OpenVPN Server

Projects

Created with an evaluation copy of Aspose.Words. To discover the full versions of our APIs please visit: https://products.aspose.com/words/

Project name: Finpulse startup

Functional descriptions: Back-End REST application for displaying financial macro indicators of a

company. Integration with 1C Enterprise, data processing and

transferring them to UI.

Technologies used: Hibernate, Postgresql, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Jackson API, Log4J,

Docker

Project name: Cinema online booking

Link: https://github.com/aborozdykh/cinema

Functional descriptions: Cinema is an application for purchasing tickets to the cinema

Technologies used: Hibernate, MySQL, Spring Security, Jackson API, Log4J

Project name: Internet Shop

Link: https://github.com/aborozdykh/internet-shop

Functional descriptions: Application with basic operations for the e-shop.

Technologies used: JDBC, MySQL, Servlet API, JSP, JSTL, Log4J

Project name: Amazon Review Application

Link: https://github.com/aborozdykh/amazon-review

Functional descriptions: Application for parsing csv file with reviews and adding them to DB

Technologies used: SpringBoot, SpringSecurity, JWT, H2, Docker

Education

Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute

Faculty of Informatics and Computer Science

Department of Computer-Aided Management and Data Processing Systems

Master's degree, Computer system analyst

Bachelor of Computer Since

Self Education

Books:

- Thinking in Java by Bruce Eckel
- Grokking Algorithms by Aditya Y. Bhargava

Algorithmic tasks:

Codewars (Java, SQL)

4 level, honor percentile 10,83 % (better than 89,17% of rest users), 150+ solved tasks

Work experience

EPAM Under NDA

Feb 2021 - present

Kyiv, Ukraine

Java Software Engineer

Created with an evaluation copy of Aspose.Words. To discover the full versions of our APIs please visit: https://products.aspose.com/words/

<u>Finpulse startup</u> Oct 2020 - Jan 2021

Kyiv, Ukraine

Java Software Engineer

Development and design of the BackEnd.

Calivita Ukraine

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

Kyiv, Ukraine

Java Software Engineer

Support of a Java application, composing SQL requests.

Part time job

LifeJoy

May 2013 - Dec 2019

Kyiv, Ukraine

Founder & Owner

- Obtaining business licenses and permits

- Signing necessary agreements and contracts for loans, services, purchase of equipment, supplies, and inventory

- Ensuring payment of creditors, employees, vendors, suppliers and taxes

- Direct marketing and advertising efforts, including promotions, displays in and around store and advertising on social media and Internet (SEO,

Google AdWords, etc)

- Enforcing rules and standards of service

- Creation, support and maintenance of an online store

Kyivstar GSM

Marth 2007 - May 2013

Kyiv, Ukraine

Senior Support Engineer

Operation and Maintenance service:

- SMS (Short Messaging Service) (work with, Linux RedHat, Oracle)

- USSD Service

- WHC Service

Coordination and communication with subcontractors for resolving problems on the systems.